Hello everybody, welcome back to Pretty Lonesome.
This week we are going to be talking about friendships and stuff.
Specifically having no fucking friends and being in your 20s because I think that it
is a common conundrum.
Conundrum's my new word by the way.
I think I'm going to start doing word of the week because I get embarrassed
when I discover a new word or I remember a new word and I use
it a lot and I feel like people are going to notice and be like,
did this witch just discover that word?
And to me that is just like a little bit embarrassing.
I don't know why.
That makes me feel like deep, deep embarrassment, like in my soul.
Well, yes, in my soul.
I'm sticking with that.
So I better just so I'm I'm better off just being like upfront about it.
Guys, I'm using the word conundrum a lot because I just remembered it exists.
Let me have it.
We'll do word of the week.
I'm going to forget to do that.
We might do word of the week.
I'll be honest with you.
We might not.
Also, my dog is next to me and I think she's about to start like
jumping and screaming because my mom's about to walk out.
So for context, I live at my mother's house, much like most people in my
age range, because the economy is fucking shit.
Now, I don't live at my mom's house because the economy shit.
I am lucky enough to be able to afford to move out if I wanted
to.
I just don't want to as a matter of principle, because what the actual fuck
do you mean the average rent for a one bed in London is 3000 pounds
a month?
I just won't pay that.
Sorry, I'm not paying that.
um no I don't know what else to tell you other than no the best
way I can describe the feeling that that digit gives me is um it doesn't
make me angry it makes me malicious like I want to very underhandedly and sneakily
uh get into the personal life of a politician um and slowly but surely
derail everything about their uh personal lives that's how it makes me feel it doesn't
make me feel like, oh, oh, oh, the rent price.
No, no.
It makes me calculated and ominous.
But do you know what I mean?
It just makes me makes me cold and calculated.
Really does.
Anyway, I have been a little bit in there.
I don't mind living with my mom.
I like it a lot.
I would rather have my own flat, but not for that price.
And I also don't really want to live in London.
So I came home temporarily to just like figure out my next move and be
like, well, I don't want to pay rent in London.
So like, let me just come home, live with my mom for a few months,
and then I'll figure out where I do want to live.
That was eight months ago.
And I just kind of still live here because it's easier.
And I feel like that's a position that a lot of people in my age
range in where they can't afford to live outside of their parents house, or if
they can afford it, it's at a stretch, they would rather save, they would rather
just figure out where they're going rather than be working paycheck to paycheck and just
kind of get so wrapped up in the stresses of everyday life that they don't
actually end up doing anything.
Most of my friends, when we all finished university, moved back to where they grew
up.
I did it.
My friends did it.
Everyone did it.
Unless you were offered a job straight out of university or you were going on
to study another course, there was just actually no fucking point because I was not
staying in Canterbury and I was not going to pay the rent in London.
So and I still am not.
So I've just been home ever since.
I moved out for six months.
I went to London for six months.
I paid an insane amount of rent.
Not as insane as it is now because that's how fast the economy is actually
fucking burning but I was still an insane amount and I went fuck this and
I ended my contract six months early and I came home and I've been here
ever since and I keep meaning to make a decision about my life but I
just keep forgetting I don't know I think she loves having me here but I'm
also like I feel bad because I know she loves having me here and I
know she doesn't like really want to live alone but I'm also like you're 60
sexy and so fun like 30 flirty and thriving but 60 sexy and so fun
that's what I was trying to do there if you didn't get it I wouldn't
blame you if you didn't but I don't know anyways it got me thinking about
why this is difficult because even though I have the access the opportunity and the
financial ability to not be in this situation I still am in this situation.
I've chosen it, but I'm still here.
And it's not ideal.
Because why the fuck am I sitting in the same bed that I had when
I was 12?
And I'm talking to the same friend I had when I was 12.
Except I used to talk to her about who said what in maths class.
And now I'm talking to her about her fucking wedding.
Like it's just genuinely moments where no matter what is actually going on in your
life, no matter how much you're progressing, no matter how many new people you've met,
how many new opportunities you've had, how much money you've made, to sit in the
same exact spot that you have been in 10 years ago is trippy as fuck
like it's actually so weird and it's also a sign that I need to get
a new mattress because that's genuinely gross but anyway I keep having these moments where
every heartbreak I've ever had ever endured I've endured it within this house because I
haven't really had that many heartbreaks but I've had enough and they all happened here
pretty much.
And the other day I was thinking about something and I was sad about it
and I was on my sofa and I was staring at my fireplace and I
realized every single version of me that's been in this exact position has sat on
this exact spot and sat at those exact bricks.
I'm literally hurt, right?
Like it was genuinely like I could feel that I had time traveled in that
moment and I was like, this is not right.
This is not natural.
I need to move out of my mother's house now because I was literally like,
whoa, I've been here before, not just on this sofa, not just in this room.
I've been exactly here before as this exact person feeling these exact emotions.
To feel the same exact emotion six years after the last time you felt it
and be staring at the exact same bricks on the exact same sofa in the
exact same, it genuinely will make you go crazy.
I was like, no, no, it's time to move out.
Anyway, all the friends that I grew up with here, I either cut them off
because they're fucking evil or they're still at university.
Most of my friends have either just graduated or they haven't graduated yet.
So when I come back here, there's actually no one for me to hang out
with because people are either off living their lives or they're still at university.
So no one's here.
And so last night I was just at home doing my thing when one of
my neighbors walked through the door and she's a girl that I grew up with.
She's my sister's best friend.
And we all grew up together, all living on the same street.
And she walked through the door with a bottle of wine and we sat around
and drank it and she told me like she's moved home for a couple of
months because she's just finished university and she's just figuring out where she's what she's
going to do next and that was the first person that has done that from
my friend group and I realized in that moment it's actually very lonely here because
you are the only person doing this with me like being back where we started
with me no one else that I know is here it got me thinking also
about how comforting that friendship is for me because she's just an old friend and
I just know her and I have to think about why or how I just
do and I just trust that she just knows me and it's like it's very
non-judgmental it's very like look I've seen you be 14 and I've seen you be
20 like we're just gonna be good with each other because if that didn't make
me hate you then we're good it's just a very relaxed like because a lot
of the times when I make newer friends I feel much more conscious of who
they are as a person because inherently I slightly distrust them I want to listen
more closely when they speak about how they view the world or how they feel
about their ex or like there's all these little things that I'm looking for a
telltale sign that the new person I met that I really like is crazy or
is evil or is something that I am not seeing but then when you've known
someone for the best part of their life like most of the time they've been
on earth and you've just watched them you don't have to ask because I've seen
you be a good person and I've seen you be genuine and I've seen everything
happen to you I've witnessed your life like I don't need to ask you questions
about your ex because I actually fucking knew him and he was fucking terrible like
it's just so much more relaxing I spend all my time almost all my time
around new people who a lot of the time do have ulterior motives with me
and I don't mind that they do, but they do.
It's just understanding that they do, whatever.
It's fine.
But it gets exhausting.
And I just haven't been around familiarity in so long that when familiarity was in
front of me, I didn't even know what it was.
And I was like, why am I finding this so sweet and comforting and cozy?
And I realized it's because I just trust you, completely trust you to be who
I know you are because I've watched you become them.
You know what I mean?
And that was really nice.
But then it got me thinking how scary it is to make friends in your
20s and how hard because a lot of people move home and there's not much
opportunity or it doesn't feel like there is anyway my experience for new friendships where
you've always been because I've already met all the bitches my age and I already
fucking hate them you know I've made I know you guys and I decided that
we are not friends that's not changing um like I'm not gonna go and find
that one girl from my class at school who I thought was all right just
because I'm lonely I'm just not going to do that.
So it's hard.
And unless you're working a job where you just get some cool co-workers, I don't
really know where else you're supposed to meet people because everyone's like, oh, pick up
a hobby.
Okay, I get the sentiment.
But genuinely, that's not going to happen.
Sorry, it's just not.
I've tried to pick up hobbies.
I picked up a hobby.
I'll tell you what I picked up.
I picked up a gym class in my small town where I grew up thinking
maybe I'll meet some nice girls my age.
Do you know who I met?
50 year olds.
There's no one my age here.
Like, I don't know where they all went because I'm sure I was at school
with them and suddenly they're gone.
Why am I still here?
This isn't fair.
This is backwards.
Anyways, I'm very relieved that they're gone though, actually, because to put it very simply,
I did not like you guys.
Well, not all of them.
Anyway, it is hard to make friends in your 20s because you just are in
less context to do it.
If it's not university and you don't get lucky with your co-workers, where the fuck
are you going to find people, right?
And to actually find people that you're compatible with is very rare.
But that's going to be a lifelong struggle.
That's not exclusive to your 20s.
It's just actually hard.
I was lucky.
I found my friend T on the street.
Literally saw her crying on the street and then we became friends.
It was that simple.
I was just walking down Oxford Street and there she was.
Picked up a stray.
With Millie, I found her on Instagram when I was 13 years old.
My very close friendships have come to me in very strange ways.
When it comes to old friendships as well, it's also very hard to keep those
intact, I think, in your 20s.
Because 20s are so scary.
First of all, you know that audio where it's like, do you know you have
30 minutes?
30!
yeah I hate that audio because it validated everything I feel and I didn't want
it to be validated I actually wanted to someone to tell me I was crazy
and that I have more than 30 minutes and then that audio came about and
I was like now I have 20 minutes like the reason I think it's so
fucking scary is because I have one friend who's still at uni getting drunk on
the weekends and the weekdays actually and um living with her friends and her boyfriend
and just like is at uni like that's the phase of her life that she's
in I have another friend who just got married I just went to my first
wedding and I was walking into the chapel and I said to the person I
was with isn't it crazy this is the first wedding and they were like what
do you mean and I was like well this is the first one to get
married like of everyone we knew and grew up with this is the first one
she's done it first from our group of friends anyway and she's like oh my
god that's crazy i was like yes now this is a girl that i used
to um jump on the trampoline with i said we have pictures of us in
the bath together at like eight years old and we wear like t-shirts and suddenly
she is saying her vows and then the most terrifying part guys oh my fucking
god actually let me just freak out for one sec so that she says her
vows and i'm looking around like why is no one saying that they object like
when they was like if anyone knows why these two should not be lawfully wed
me hello this is a child marriage and it's not legal why was everyone okay
with it like no word of advice no are you okay no you know you
know you've got i it's that you're very young none of that why because it's
a perfectly reasonable age to get married it's not actually i i don't i don't
disagree that you should can get married or make that decision at 25 that's how
old my friend is.
I think that's actually very fine.
Nora Smith's some kind of age like that.
I don't know.
It's disputed.
I love her though.
But afterwards, when the wedding was done, I was stood around with some older women
talking about they wanted to know what I did on Instagram.
So we're having that conversation.
And innately, when I have that conversation with people older, I feel very fucking young
because they're like, so what do you do for work?
And I'm like, well, I post online and they're like oh so like like instagram
and i'm like yeah essentially instagram they're like well how does that make you money
and i'm like well you just have to imagine me like a billboard like a
talking one and they get it now that makes me feel like i might be
15 years old telling someone yeah my line of work is i just like take
pictures of myself and like film stuff that i do then the bride comes and
we're like you know what the fuck oh my fucking podcast sorry that was my
grandma um she just got out of a taxi and walked past my car and
literally not about to explain to her what a podcast is right now I had
to duck and hide that's so mean of me sorry I'm gonna go say hi
to her in a minute I had no idea she was coming over right now
anyway so I'm there feeling very youthful because I'm just trying to explain the internet
to like a 60 year old woman who knows what the internet is by the
way but she's like how do you what do you mean you work as yourself
on the internet and I'm like okay so it's not porn I feel that there's
a big age gap between us in those moments you know what I mean because
there is and then the bride comes up and she we're all complimenting her dress
and I realize no one's asking her or no one is commenting on how young
she is and now I'm not her age so I'm just like yeah she's fucking
old anyone older than me is fucking old i've always stood on that i think
when i was 12 a 13 year old was really fucking old and now a
25 year old ew don't i couldn't date one that would be illegal like i
just and don't even get me started on 30 year olds i don't know what
the stick up my butt about them is actually let me not get into it
because it's so fucking mean i've always had a vendetta against 30 year olds and
i i really don't know why but she's 25 so i'm like yeah okay we're
not the same age so I'm not maybe I don't get it I don't know
we're close enough I should probably know exactly why I feel this way like I
am close enough in age too that it's negligible it's not like I'm fucking 16
and like yeah 25 is old no like I'm gonna be 25 in in you
know a matter of minutes it feels so I should probably not be thinking that
she's old it's just the way that all these 50 year old 60 year old
women were not like god you know so young you know crazy youth crazy kids
you know what a passionate marriage and you know do you think how is it
gonna work you're so young none of that just I love the flyers flyers when
I did you make the food she catered though the bride catered the wedding herself
and everyone was just talking about the food and the flyers and the flowers and
the dress not the fact that she's literally 12 because she's not 12 that was
where I came to in my head oh my god you're not 12 terrifying and
then I still have a friend that's like almost the same age as her who's
still at university um you know what I mean and then I just broke up
with someone obviously fucking hell in such a extreme manner but I was like this
is fine I'm young like I'm not supposed to be fucking getting married or like
knowing anything yeah you know although I will say I think that that was the
last bad breakup I can do because I think after a certain age it does
get embarrassing like that one was fine I got into that relationship when I was
21.
So I'm like, okay, you know, that is excusable.
I think if I did that again, because that's my third bad one, by the
way, that was not a first time rodeo for me.
That was my third horrendous end to a relationship, or just horrendous relationship in general.
So I was coming to all these realizations of one, I have 30 minutes.
Two, if I wanted to get married or pregnant today, no one would ask me
if I'm crazy.
Oh, no, they would, I think.
Pregnancy, I think would be, people might still be like wow it's very young but
marriage for some reason that's fine and obviously I know people that get married at
like 20 18 even 16 even oh I don't think I see you got that
I think it is I think you can they did it on Coronation Street Sophie
and Sian got married on Coronation Street when they were 16 actually I think they
got uh the the didn't get married that was the whole issue they got a
ceremony of something although they actually never did because Sian ran off.
So, bit o' law if you are into Coronation Street.
Anyway, crazy.
So, I find it very hard to understand how old I am because I, first
of all, I'm pretty sure in my head I've always been 16.
I will be 16 probably forever.
So, the fact that I'm just not 16 is upsetting because, what do you mean?
Second of all, am I supposed to be getting married or can I just like
still hang out with my friends at university and go get drunk on a Wednesday
because that's when the student union gets drunk you know what I mean like where
am I um everyone is so different and it's really really scaring me and then
do you want to know the most upsetting thing that happened to me I'm very
used very I'm very used to being the youngest in a room when it comes
to like the people that I work with because I'm the one that does the
fucking shit posting and they're the ones with the real jobs who you know get
me deals or like do my audio stuff like whoever it is they're always older
than me I'm very used to being the youngest in the room so imagine my
shock and horror when um one of my PR girls was uh younger than me
I was like whoa okay when did that happen like so you're telling me people
my age can have jobs as good as yours that's like that means you've had
life experience and school experience and you're very capable crazy it just keeps catching up
to me where I'm like I'm actually not 16 but I think that the the
fact that everyone is at different stages of their lives some people are at square
one and it feels like other people are just further down the road and whether
that be that they have like an amazing job or they're fucking married or they
have a baby whatever it is none of my kids have babies yet thank god
because everyone's at such different points in their lives it's hard to even have friendships
because I might have a friend that I've had for five years um and now
I'm fresh out of uni at an early stage of my career and she is
settling down and renting a house with a man and getting pregnant.
I don't have that experience but I imagine someone does because that can happen.
It's a possibility.
How confusing.
Like even if it's someone you get on with, even if it's a really really
good friend, life is just genuinely so open to choices right now.
You can choose anything you want that people will just go off in different directions
and you will lose friends not because they did anything wrong just because they got
married.
All of my friends are at a place in their life right now where they're
just focusing on their careers and everyone's at very early stages.
Most of my friends are not in jobs that they love or want to work
in forever.
That's just like the way it is.
They are just doing things as stepping stones to get where they really want to
be.
A lot of people feel very discontented.
I think that's the word.
And I noticed that there's more anxiety around my friends and their careers than there
was two years ago when we were all still at university because like I've said
before university really is a time where as stressed as you are about deadlines and
as stressed as you are about just everything in general there isn't this existential stress
of like who am I what am I gonna make for myself for my life
because I don't have to think about it right now because I'm here for the
next two years right like I don't have to worry about the next step right
now I just have to focus on what I'm doing and I'm content with that
then once you finish it's just this panic that fucking hits you in the face
I had it too because when I finished university this was not my job it
was something I did it was a hobby it was really fun and cute it
was not paying me any money so I well it was but like not money
that I would want to live off of forever and I had to make a
decision like do I want to try and do this full time and just like
take a year off and travel a bit which is what I ended up doing
because I wanted to go travel with Millie or do I not want to have
a gap in my resume what were you doing for an entire fucking year of
your life you didn't have any job because I was posting on TikTok, sorry.
Like if it didn't go well I would have had a gap in my resume
and that wasn't okay there's definitely like a buzz of anxiety around my friends and
I think it's healthy because they're concerned and they like I think it's just it's
a sign of ambition but people are just going off in different directions I have
so many friends who have moved away from where we all went to university I
have friends who have moved away from home who are still at university who are
just everywhere and it's just hard also when you move out of an environment that
has become familiar to you like university I would go around campus and I would
just see familiar faces all the time I would see people that I knew not
necessarily liked but I knew and I had flatmates and I had housemates and I
had coursemates and I just knew all these faces and I just it was familiar
to me like everything was familiar to me it was a world that I had
been living in for long enough that I knew everything and everyone pretty much not
everything and that is like that's actually a hard thing to lose because you just
kind of lose this sense of belonging this sense of like community warmth whatever it
is like it's not there anymore and it's healthy because obviously you're supposed to you
know fly from the nest and whatever and go into unfamiliar waters and uncomfortable situations
because that is how you grow and that is how you get a new job
and that is how you become who you were meant to be but it is
uncomfortable and I think it just contributes to everyone being really lonely in their 20s
also I always remember when I was like 19 to 21 I had expected for
some reason during those years because it was like early university I expected that I
was gonna find my best friend in life because I feel like it's a common
thing in like movies and stuff and like you just hear about it of like,
I met my best friends at university.
I met my kids' aunt at university.
And so I had always been like, okay, well, that's when I have to find
the girl that is my soulmate platonically so that my kids can have that because
that's just kind of what I expected.
Like, okay, it's going to be the most social few years of my life, university,
duh.
And well, little did I fucking know that was not the case.
But I thought it was going to be the most social few years of my
life I thought it was going to be the most open most new experiences most
diversity of every kind of experience you could imagine that just you just don't usually
get and so I expected like if I'm gonna find her she's gonna be at
university with me she was not I think a lot of people know the value
of friendship in this day and age like I genuinely think that I'm seeing a
shift and maybe I'm wrong correct me if I am but I feel like a
lot of people are shifting in between putting more value on men and boyfriends and
relationships in general to their girlfriends I think I just see it on social media
a lot of people really valuing their female friendships a lot more.
I think that there is so much more to be acknowledged even now when it
comes to how important friendships are.
Because I think a lot of people in my age group feel lonely and their
first instinct is get on Hinge, get on Tinder, like find relationship, find partner.
And I think that's actually why a lot of relationships don't fucking work because you
just can't enter it like that.
like you cannot need something and so then you get a partner to fulfill it
like you have to be self-sufficient you have to have enough options for that need
to be met that it doesn't just fall on one person like go out get
friends continue your life and then find someone who fits into it do not find
someone who you can then form a life around because that's just never gonna fucking
work it's never gonna work but I do think that people are really like starting
to acknowledge the importance of friendships especially female friendships but I think it's also hard
just once you do find a friend say you you get past the hardest hurdle
and you find a girl that you want to be friends with you're gonna have
different jobs most likely like it's hard to find people who fit in the same
city similar job similar life similar person it's just like so many puzzle pieces have
to fall into place if they're not falling into place for you I genuinely believe
that there's a reason and maybe you just need to spend some time by yourself
because maybe that is just what you're supposed to do right now I have had
periods of my life where I've had no fucking friends like and it's not like
oh I fell out with all my friends it's like yeah I have friends but
they're nowhere near me right now they're off doing their own thing I just don't
have anyone close to me that I like and it's really lonely and it's actually
very hard and I I do look back on those times in my life as
like yeah that was hard but the things that I learned from those times was
so valuable to me and I just built a very very very strong bond with
myself probably too strong because I think that I still to this day I'm like
very much someone who will be like I don't need you like I don't care
what it is you supply for me I don't need you I do need my
friends but like I think I restrict information from my friends because I'm like let
me deal with this on my own I think to prove that I can to
myself not to them but I'm just like yeah let mean like withhold this information
from you so that I am not completely dependent on you or reliant in any
way which is dumb because I do want to rely on my friends and I
do rely on my friends a lot of the time it's just sometimes I'm actually
insane sorry like I said I am living at home and I'm by myself and
my friend is here as well she's just moved home she she's got me but
there's no one else really here majorly that like actually she has probably more friends
than I do live mine um so as I said I was thinking about how
it is just hard to have to go out into the world go to university
and then come back home because I think so many people do it I do
it I done it and it is hard it's lonely it's it's difficult to readjust
to being around parents it is a little bit fucking depressing it's mentally challenging and
it is also just I can feel a bit hopeless I now have the option
where I can leave if I want to I just haven't got around to it
yet but when I didn't have the option when I couldn't afford to leave and
I was here after university it felt very very very dark and as much as
I love my mom and I love her house and it's always been big enough
for me before it just wasn't big enough for me anymore and I didn't want
to feel like sound ungrateful or you know seem frustrated or tell anyone that I
was frustrated because at least I have a fucking roof over my head it just
felt dark and it felt lonely and it felt hopeless and it felt like what
was the point I worked so hard at university and now I may as well
have just not gone because I'm just in the same exact position I was in
when I left four years ago and now I'm also in debt I think that
position is genuinely hard and and I think the main thing to remember if if
you are in that kind of a place is nothing's real and more people are
aware you think than they will tell you if that makes sense I'm not gonna
be specific when I say this but I'm gonna share a secret with you which
is I would genuinely say that over half of popular people online
not only do they not have fucking friends it's not like oh they've got fake
friends a lot of people have fake friends no I'm talking like these people they
do not have friends and they do not have social lives and they want they
want these things but they don't have it and they just make it look like
they do.
They don't have most of the things that they show.
This does not go for everyone, by the way.
It's just something that when I first came in to this kind of industry, I
started meeting these people and I started to understand this is not real.
I used to feel really insecure.
For example, when I first came into this kind of life and job, I remember
seeing that everyone somehow could afford things I couldn't, but it seemed like they should
be being paid similar to how I was being paid.
And yet they had a house and a car and all these clothes and all
these friends and all this, this and that.
And they were always abroad and they always doing all these things.
And I was like, damn, like, am I not getting paid?
Like, who do I need to speak to to like, you know, get on the
fucking salary or on like, did I get a salary?
But like, there was a big disconnect.
And I'm not talking the difference in five or 10,000 pounds, extra money.
I'm talking millions difference.
And I was very confused.
And one of the things I realized very quickly was most of them are nepotism.
And that's why they have those things.
And it's not that there's a pay difference.
It's just they've always lived like that.
That was one.
Number two, it's not real.
And when I tell you it's not real, I mean, these bitches rent their cars,
they rent their houses, and they rent their bags, and they rent their t-shirts.
It's insane.
And when I tell you it is deranged it is I respect it because I'm
like wow like you are actually just putting on a production this is actually the
Truman Show but opposite it's opposite day at the Truman Show no one else knows
only you know that this is a performance and maybe I was dumb for not
knowing that and for thinking they really had these social lives and like some people
do like don't get me wrong there's a lot of people who do and I
am in awe of them because I'm like wow but a lot of the time
more than you would think and in contexts that you would be shocked about I
just can't tell you because I'm not about to actually get fucking sued it's for
real like that's the bottom line and it's easy to feel like shit about your
life and about yourself when you are in your 20s because there's so much comparison
there is so much variation either you might feel quite good about yourself because at
least you're not on your seventh year of uni because you didn't retake maybe you
feel good about yourself because you don't want to fucking get married and you feel
bad for the girl that just did that you just seen on Facebook or the
girl who's pregnant and you're like glad that's not me and then equally you might
feel like shit about yourself because someone in your same age group is talking about
their latest promotion and their linkedin profile is literally on fucking crack and they somehow
have disposable income for a vacation that's another thing people will talk a big game
about how broke they are and then they'll go on fucking vacation that never made
any sense to me it's the same thing as at school when people be like
yeah i didn't study for this test and the next thing you know they have
an A+.
What do you mean?
I thought we were in this together and you just made me feel like we're
the same so I should feel like shit about the fact that I'm not doing
as well as you and now I realise you were lying to me and that's
what your 20s are you're just being lied to I think 20s just are lonely
for people because of the nature of them like jobs people are very movable transferable
they go to new cities they go to new places they go to new countries
they go home they leave home there's literally nowhere you're meant to be so you
just everyone is at a different point in their lives it's hard to not feel
like shit about it sometimes.
I'm actually the same way.
I see people in my age group who are rampantly more successful, more rich, more
put together than I am.
And I'm like, fuck the hell.
And that's fine.
I'm not them.
And they're not me.
I just, there's no point feeling like shit about it because it becomes a self-fulfilling
prophecy.
And it shouldn't because your 20s are meant to be for being lost, for figuring
shit out.
You're very, very young.
Like, I feel like that's actually forgotten a lot, especially online, because you're having conversations
about being 22 with someone that's 15.
And so in comparison, you feel like you're old.
You're 22.
I need you to sit with that for a sec.
The 15 year old literally isn't allowed to travel alone.
That's how young they are.
That's a child.
You're 22.
The way I look at 20s, you're a toddler.
So you start at zero on your 20th birthday you just got born if you're
22 or two years old you're 23 or three years old if you're 24 you're
four years old that's how I look at them because it's literally like you start
again I don't know what it is I genuinely felt it on my 20th birthday
I felt like my brain went blank and I started again and you know what
I was actually talking about with my friends the other day this is how fucking
stupid I am I say that I think it's for rediscovering things that should be
innate knowledge for example the other day my friend was visiting me in London and
she and I are on the same ADHD medication.
And so I was asking her about it.
I was like, do you get really tired at lunchtime as well?
Like I literally get so fucking exhausted at 3 p.m.
every single day.
And my friend was like, yeah, I used to get that.
Have you tried eating lunch?
And I was like, no, why would I do that?
And she was like, well, your energy crash in the middle of the day might
just mean that you need fuel, which is food.
So you should probably eat and then your medication will probably last longer and you'll
just feel better generally.
and I was like whoa a meal in the middle of the day because I
need extra fuel this is revolutionary and I decided I was gonna pick up lunch
I've never I've never been a lunch person it genuinely can I say something crazy
lunch is yellow and 30 year olds are lunch they are all synonymous to me
and I don't like any of them I'm so sorry I feel 30 I genuinely
have nothing against you I don't know what it is but it's the same way
I feel about yellow um we all collectively there was actually four people in the
room when we had this conversation and all of us rediscovered the fact that lunch
is important together and then my friend was like my mum always tells me that
your 20s are for remembering things that you've actually been taught your entire life and
it's so true because why was my friend telling me have you tried lunch a
revolutionary piece of advice that I would have paid for like that's the kind of
insight that I am talking about yes lunch you're so right anyway I think that
I think that your 20s are scary they are lonely and I think that that
is not unhealthy this one just got married and this one just kissed a girl
for the first time you know what I mean there's no way you're meant to
be you are exactly where you're meant to be you're not behind in your career
you're not behind because you moved home you're not behind because you can barely afford
your rent or you can't afford your rent you're Exactly where you're supposed to be,
I think, at all times throughout your life.
It's your life.
Someone else's.
Why would you be supposed to be somewhere that you're not?
I don't understand.
Who told you that?
Did they give you a schedule?
No?
Okay then.
Relax.
And if you feel like you have no fucking friends, don't worry about it.
Because, I'll tell you what, I don't have any fucking friends.
I have two, maybe three at a push.
I have...
Actually, I'm lying.
I have two amazing friends who live nowhere near me.
Actually, I have three amazing friends that live nowhere near me because Millie doesn't live
anywhere near me.
I have three amazing friends who live nowhere near me.
and I love that I have them in my life I just never see them
and I rarely speak to them I know they're always there and then I have
a friend who does live very near me and I see her all the time
and she's like my person that's my roster entirely there's nothing else I have a
lot of acquaintances and stuff but those are my friends and I'm someone who has
literally probably every possibility to make a new friend I could genuinely I think I'm
in a unique position where if I wanted a new friend I could probably find
one the same day.
Like if I really put my back into it, you know what I mean?
Like I could probably find someone that like there's so much scope, even just like
I get invited to a lot of places.
Okay, perfect.
Like I'll make a friend there.
It's not because you're unlikable or it's not because you're, it's hard.
It's because it just is hard to make friends.
They are as serious as romantic relationships and you wouldn't ever expect someone to have
a romantic, you wouldn't expect someone to have a romantic relationship, but you would expect
them to have a friend why what's the difference like it's just as intense for
me anyway a lot of the time I know they're different but it should not
be an expectation at all points in your life to be surrounded by friends because
sometimes you won't be that's okay you'll be fine because they'll find you at some
point they're out there right now they're becoming the people that they need to be
so that when you meet them you like them that's always what I think I'm
like you know how I think about that actually I always think about that in
the context of my future husband or wife because obviously I don't know who they
are right now but I know that they're out there somewhere and I'm like what
are you doing freak you better not be fucking freaking out with someone else it's
disgusting but it's like I know that they if I met that person today whoever
I'm eventually going to marry I probably wouldn't like them very much unless I'm meant
to meet them today but I probably more than likely would not like them very
much because they are not who I'm going to meet yet they're not the version
of themselves that will collide with my life and there's a reason that I haven't
met them yet because I would meet them and I think you fucking suck or
you don't intrigue me or you're not my type because maybe my type's gonna change
there's always a reason I don't know you yet and I'm glad I don't because
they probably have some shit to sort out because I'm definitely not gonna date one
of those freaks that's like I actually have a very like consistent linear life and
like I feel like I've always been this person no I'm gonna date someone that's
like well I have had seven different eras and I can only access knowledge about
three of them through hypnotherapy that will be who I marry so I hope they're
okay right now I'm having a good morning because they're probably not not gonna lie
because I'm not getting married until I'm like 60 so oh they could be doing
anything it's actually a crazy thought well now I will be driving to London because
I'm going to go and cat sit for my friend T she's going to Geneva
so that's fun and and little ADHD medication update I had an appointment with my
psychiatrist this morning and she had upped my dose last time to 40 milligrams of
my medication and then she'd give me a booster to take in the afternoon because
I kept crashing and crash is basically like imagine like an actual come down I
was angry irritated exhausted um all by 3 p.m because the medication wore off before
it was meant to so she gave me a booster so I started taking that
and I was like it's okay I don't crash anymore which is nice but I
I don't think I'm focused I think I'm just slightly more regulated question mark like
I just I'm not I'm just a little more rational that's the best way I
can describe it life is okay and I'm not freaking out majorly about anything which
is very unusual for me so I was like okay I know it's working I
just it's not making me do my work it's not making me sit at my
computer and focus for an hour which is what I need it for like I
don't mind being a crazy bitch actually I do because I didn't realize I was
that crazy until I got on this medication and it just like and I was
like oh that's nice that's nice life my existence doesn't have to be a horrendous
bloody fight crazy but I told her like I don't really feel that focus though
and she's like okay well I'll just like up you way more she's like since
this didn't work I'm gonna make you try make you try she's now given me
the dose up and then double dose in the afternoon so I'm gonna take more
in the morning and then the booster that she's gonna give me is more akin
to a rocket ship up my butthole imagine that um and I get to try
it today time I'm literally so scared because I have to drive to London so
I'm like I'm not gonna fucking drive this and then go driving because actually I
don't think that that's legal I'm not sure but I'm obviously just not gonna try
new medication and then get behind a wheel that would be silly so I'm gonna
go to London and then the second that I park my car in London I'm
gonna try the new medication that she put me on and I'm really hopeful that
it's going to work this time because I'm getting a little bit scared that the
dose keeps going up and I just still I'm fucking useless the best way I
can describe it I'm still completely incapable of getting shit done um not completely but
effectively capeless capeless capable I'm really hoping that this new dose is going to work
because I'm getting scared I'm like because I googled it and it was like some
people's body chemistry literally just does not work with this pill it just won't help
them that scared me there's another type of medication I can try if this one
doesn't work.
And a lot of people find that only one of them works for them, rather
than having them both be like, oh, yeah, I could take either.
It's like, no, I prefer this one over this one.
So if this one doesn't work, I will try the second option.
I'm just skilled.
And I really hope that it works.
Because all it keeps doing is making me feel like I've had caffeine.
Like I get a burst of energy and like jitters almost, but like that does
not make me focus.
It just kind of makes me want to go somewhere?
Question mark?
Like it makes me want to maybe have a conversation but that's it so anyway
my dog is actually sleeping next to me right now and she's just fucking ripped
ass it stinks thank you for listening to this week's episode of pretty lonesome i
hope that you enjoyed it i'm gonna go drive to london now and then potentially
i'm gonna go try my new medication and then i'll let you guys know what
it does because it's a significantly larger amount than i was on before so if
i start posting things on my instagram story that just make you feel like slightly
uncomfortable like did she mean to post that.
That's how you know it worked.
See you guys next week.
I love you so much.
Have a good week.
Bye.